Parents who had applied
online for their children's admission in Kendriya Vidyalaya,
if you had
any issue in choosing the school, if you have
chosen the wrong school, if you have any other
issue, then in that case, 21
March 2025 is still the last date for
online admission in Class 1 in Kendriya Vidyalaya.
If you want to
cancel your previous application, then you
can cancel it and submit a new application, it will still be valid. So, if
you feel that you
want to cancel the previous application, if there is
any problem in it, then for that,
first of all you have to come to the home page
of Kendriya Vidyalaya, then after this it
is written login here, you have to log in, as
you click on the login button, then
here you have to fill the login code, date of birth,
mobile number and captcha.
You have also received all this information through your message
and you must have kept its photo by clicking on it, then
you will fill all the details in it,
then you will be redirected to the new
interface here.  But you get two options, the
first is View Submitted Application, here
you will see all the details of the application you submitted, if you
want to cancel it, then you
will click on Cancel Application, as if you
click on Cancel Application, it is
written here that do you want to cancel
this submitted application, so here it is Yes
Cancel, if you click on it, then
a window comes to you, you will
receive the mobile number which you had given at the
time of registration, as you fill the OTP and
captcha, then after this you have to
click on Yes Cancel the Application, as soon as
you click,
you will see a new interface here and
here it is written that the application is cancelled
at 18320 25, so if you
want to reapply, it is written here that reply
with
prefilled from submitted application, this
means that if you want to apply again
but you do
not have to fill all the information again, then you can go and
click on it.  You can see all your details
and if you
reply here fresh, fresh means that
you will have to submit it in a completely fresh manner,
if you do not
want to waste much time then you will click on reply with data prefilled
from last submitted application, as
soon as you click,
you will see here that
all your last entries have
come for updation, if you feel that
you can update within these details then you can do it even now,
friend, here you
can see that all the details are available with me
for updating, so you
can update all the details here, thank you.